[
    {
        "question": "2 + 2?",
        "answer": 4
      },
      {
        "question": "5 * 7?",
        "answer": 35
      },
      {
        "question": "10 - 3?",
        "answer": 7
      },
      {
        "question": "12 * 7?",
        "answer": 84
      },
      {
        "question": "3 + 6?",
        "answer": 9
      },
      {
        "question": "15 - 9?",
        "answer": 6
      },
      {
        "question": "9 * 5?",
        "answer": 45
      },
      {
        "question": "20 + 3?",
        "answer": 23
      },
      {
        "question": "14 - 7?",
        "answer": 7
      },
      {
        "question": "6 * 9?",
        "answer": 54
      },
      {
        "question": "25 + 12?",
        "answer": 37
      },
      {
        "question": "8 * 4?",
        "answer": 32
      },
      {
        "question": "15 + 27?",
        "answer": 42
      },
      {
        "question": "7 * 9?",
        "answer": 63
      },
      {
        "question": "48 / 6?",
        "answer": 8
      },
      {
        "question": "25 / 5?",
        "answer": 5
      },
      {
        "question": "12 + 15 - 7?",
        "answer": 20
      },
      {
        "question": "9 * 4 + 6?",
        "answer": 42
      },
      {
        "question": "18 / 3 + 5?",
        "answer": 11
      }
]